(Penny:)I know.
(Sheldon:)Although I've always hated
how my right frontal lobe looks in pictures.
(Beverley:)Common complaint among men.
(Beverley:)Nothing's ever big enough.
Except when they get a tumor.
Then you never hear the end of it.
Yeah, I'd love to see
a scan of your brain sometime.
(Beverley:)Oh, I'll send you a link,
but its physiology is fairly unimpressive.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I can't believe that.
(Beverley:)Your unwillingness to accept empirical
evidence suggests an attempt at flattery.
(Sheldon:)My apologies.
(Sheldon:)I've been living with your son too long.
Gotten into some bad habits.
(Sheldon:)Understandable.
(Sheldon:)Can I make you a cup of tea?
(Beverley:)I doubt it, but if anyone has a chance,
it's probably you.
(Sheldon:)I feel very comfortable around you.
(Beverley:)I feel very comfortable around you too.
(Sheldon:)It's surprising because I generally
don't feel comfortable around...